most of them in homes.
Many of these deaths could have been
prevented by a smoke alarm.
That is why the Professional Association
of Firefighter Technicians
supports the Europe smoke Alarm Day campaign.
These devices, which can be easily
purchased in commercial establishments,
These devices, which can be easily purchased
in commercial establishments,
are very easy to install and also inexpensive.
Installing a smoke alarm in our homes
can really save our lives.
That is why we insist and encourage people to use
these devices, installing them in their home.
I am Victor Manuel Fernandez,
Vice President of the Professional Association
of Firefighter Technicians
chief of the Fuenlabrada Fire Department, in Madrid, Spain
Thank you very much.